# **BURCU SAHIN**

# COMPUTER ENGINEERING

- Date of birthday: 02/01/2000 Phone number: +90 533 287 0226
- Email adress: mkalantar01@gmail.com LinkedIn: www.linkedin.com/in/burcu-k-253219107
- Github: https://github.com/burcuklntr

## Education

- Lokman Hekim High School
- Iskenderun Technical
  University
  Computer engineering

2018 - 2024

## **SKILLS**

- Adobe Photoshop
- HTML-CSS
- Tailwind Css
- REACT
- Capcut Canva

# Languages

- English B1
- German A7

### Certificate

- YDS ACADEMY ENGLISH COURSE B1 CERTIFICATE
- TEOL DIL OKULLARI GERMAN COURSE

A1 CERTIFICATE

CERTIFICATE

ROOM OF COMPUTER

ENGINEEPS

ENGINEERS
IZMIR BMO SUMMER CAMP

# About me

I graduated from Iskenderun Technical University Computer Engineering Department. I have been trying to work on Adobe Photoshop, Illustrator and After Effects for 1-2 years. I have months of experience as a video editor. My graduation project is about image processing. I have 3-4 websites that I made with React and Tailwind CSS.

# WORK EXPERIENCE

#### INTERN

Teknokent - Turkey/Adana - 07.2019-08.2019

 A simple automation program by doing a voluntary internship on C# and Sql I developed.

#### Intern

Teknokent - Turkey/ Adana - 07.2022-08.2022

 I became interested in Adobe After Effect, concentrated on the program, and learned how to prepare short videos, edit, make presentations, and make short promotional films.

# **Projects**

#### Web site

React ve Tailwind CSS kullanarak NBC adlı web sitesini sıfırdan geliştirdim ve sitenin tamamen responsive olmasını sağladım. Mobil cihazlarda farklı bir navbar yapısı oluşturarak kullanıcı deneyimini optimize ettim, sayfa yönlendirmeleri ve çoklu kart sistemi gibi dinamik özellikler ekledim .Ayrıca, hover.dev'den dropdown görseli için ilham alarak kullanıcı arayüzünü zenginlestirdim

https://github.com/burcukIntr/NBC-Web-Site

### Web site

HTML ve Tailwind CSS kullanarak 'Mobilya' adlı bir web sitesi geliştirdim. Tailwind CSS ile modern bir arayüz tasarladım, HTML ile site yapısını oluşturdum. Ayrıca Material Icons kullanarak ikonlarla görsel öğeleri zenginleştirdim ve sitenin responsive olmasını sağlayarak farklı ekran boyutlarında tutarlı bir kullanıcı deneyimi sundum

GitHub Projesi: Mobilya